Guide to the Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive, 1960-2004 (Bulk 1973-2000) MSS.221
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Manuscripts from the Semiotext(e) Archive, 174638
  - Subseries A: Manuscripts, 174639
    - Amaduzzi, Isabella (Untitled ms), 1999; 188657 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Appelfeld, Aharon "Beyond Despair" (Introduction), c.1994; 188658 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Arcade, Penny (Interview by Chris Kraus), undated; 188659 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - [Arcade], Penny (Untitled ms), undated; 188660 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Artaud, Antonin "To Pass Final Judgement on God" (transl. David Rattray), c.1985; 188661 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Ashby, Ronny "The Cutmouth Lady", undated; 188662 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Auster, Paul "Wall Writing", undated; 188663 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Ayden, Erje "Memoirs of a Past and Present, Unwritten", 1991; 188664 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Balaban, Oded "The Paradox of the Meno and Plato's Theory of Recollection", undated; 188665 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Ballard, J.G. "Jane Fonda's Augmentation Mammoplasty", undated; 188666 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - [Banham, Reyner] "Los Angeles: The Architecture of Four Ecologies- Epilogue 1982", 188667 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Barg, Barbara "Fresh Out of Nodland", 1987; 188668 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Barg, Barbara "July", undated; 188669 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Barg, Barbara "Walk in New York City", undated; 188670 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Bateson, Gregory "Story of the Double Bind", 1976; 188671 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Baudrillard, Jean (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), 1980s; 188672 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "UBU" or "Artaud and Pataphysics", c.1995; 188673 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Baudrillard, Jean (Revisions for unknown ms), c.1995; 188674 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "From Radical Incertitude, or Thought as Imposter", 1997; 188675 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "Towards the Vanishing Point of Art" (Original text for Whitney lecture), c.1997; 188676 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "Oublier Artaud" (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), c.1999; 188677 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "Dropping out of History" (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated; 188678 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "L'euphorie sous perfusion", undated; 188679 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "L'extase de la communication", undated; 188680 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "La gauche divine", undated; 188681 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - [Baudrillard, Jean] "Metaphysique de l'otage", undated; 188682 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "USA '80", undated; 188683 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Behenna, [Veralynn] "May 20, 1992", c.1992; 188721 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Bellamy, David (Untitled ms), c.1992; 188722 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Bellour, Raymond (Interview with Deleuze and Guattari- Unpublished), 1972; 188723 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Betensky, Carolyn and Robert Callahan "Rituals of Transparency", undated; 188724 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Bifo (Untitled proofs), 1993; 188725 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Blumenthal, Henry "Mobius Love", undated; 188726 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - [Boltanski, Luc] "Entretien avec Pierre Morhange", undated; 188727 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Bouillon, Victor J. "Bio/Closure", undated; 188728 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Broderick, David "Rose Forrest Rose", c.1990; 188729 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Brown, Martin "Vanishing Return", undated; 188730 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Brown, Trisha (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated; 188731 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Brownstein, Michael "A Touch", 1991; 188732 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Breuer, Lee "The Shaggy Dog Animation" (with S.L. marginalia), 1978; 188733 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Breuer, Lee "Book of Love", undated; 188734 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Burroughs, William "The Limits of Control", undated; 188735 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Carlin, John "Nietzshe Interview", undated; 188736 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Carter, Michael "Remarks on the 1st Five Year Plan", undated; 188737 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Chabert, Elizabeth Allen "Transforming Impact: The Shock Experience in Dada and Surrealist Poetry" (dissertation), 1995; 188738 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Chabert, Elizabeth Allen "Transforming Impact: The Shock Experience in Dada and Surrealist Poetry" (dissertation), 1995; 188739 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Chabert, Elizabeth Allen "Transforming Impact: The Shock Experience in Dada and Surrealist Poetry" (dissertation), 1995; 188740 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Charyn, Jerome (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), c.1984; 188741 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Cixous, Helene "Reponses tant bien que mal" (transl. [Roz Morris]), 1997; 188742 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Cobey, Patricia "I Have Often Dreamed of Arriving Alone in a Strange Country", undated; 188743 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Cohen, Josh "Late Mailer, Baudrillard, and the Technological Disintegration of the Public Sphere", undated; 188744 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Cohen, Sande "Notes on K. Ross' Review of Premises", undated; 188745 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Crevel, Rene "Difficult Death" (transl. David Rattray), c.1984; 188746 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Daitch, Susan "Incunabula", 1985; 188747 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Dali, Salvador "Oui 1 & 2" (transl. Yvonne Shafir), undated; 188748 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Dean, Kenneth and Brian Massumi "The Elimination of Strength", undated; 188749 (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Debord, Guy "La societe du spectacle" (English film script), 2005; 188750 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Deleuze, Gilles "Presence and Function of the Spider Madness", [1973]; 188751 (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - Deleuze, Gilles "Nietzsche's Philosophy" (transl. James Leigh, Desert Islands), 2002; 188752 (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - Deleuze, Gilles "Two Regimes of Madness" (final transl. Robert Hardwick Weston), undated; 188753 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Diaz, George "On Crime Scenes", 1983-6; 188754 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Diaz, George "On Crime Scenes", 188755 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Dick, Leslie "Death by Drowning" (extract), 1991; 188756 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Dobbs, Bob "Phatic Communication with Bob Dobbs", 1997; 188757 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Dubuffet, Jean "Anticultural Positions", 1951; 188758 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Duden, Anne and Clea Wallis "Why Don't We Laugh When We Tickle Ourselves", undated; 188759 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - [Durbin, Shannon] "Nine West Girls", undated; 188760 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Duschke, Rudi "La bombe genetique", undated; 188761 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Elber, Mark "Lost and Found" and other poems, undated; 188762 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Emerling, Susan "Julie", 1990; 188763 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Flanagan, Bob "The Pain Journal" (Proofs), 1990; 188764 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Flanagan, Bob "The Pain Journal" (Proofs), 1990; 188765 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Fletcher, Jim (Various), undated; 188766 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Foreman, Richard "Perspectives of Real Time", undated; 188767 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Foreman, Richard (On Stein), undated; 188768 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Foucault, Michel "Discourse and Truth" (Original for "Fearless Speech"), 1983; 188769 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Foucault, Michel "Fearless Speech" (Proof), 1998; 188770 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Foucault, Michel "On Infantile Sexuality", undated; 188771 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Franklin, Jean "The Speech of Power" (transl. Phil Beitchman), c.1980; 188772 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Gallo, Ruben "Losing One's Head: Julia Kristeva and Decapitation", undated; 188773 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Garnet, Eldon "The Garden of Failure: Writing Brooke Sheilds", c.1995; 188774 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Garnet, Eldon "Allegory", undated; 188775 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Garrett, Daniel "The Cultural Politics Discussion Group, Gestures Toward an American Utopia", 1993; 188776 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Gente, Peter and Heidi Paris et. al "Atalanta Interviews", c.1984; 188777 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Georges, Margaret "Dada's Unclean Cuisine", 1987; 188778 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Gilbert-Lemonte, Roger (Various poems transl. David Rattray), undated; 188779 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Gilbert-Rolfe, Jeremy "Nietzschean Critique and the Hegelian Commodity", 1997; 188780 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Gilbert-Rolfe, Jeremy "Beauty and the Contemporary Sublime", undated; 188781 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Godzich, Wlad "University Seminar on the Theory of Literature", 1974; 188782 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Guattari, Felix (Transcript of an unpublished lecture), 1970s; 188783 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Guattari, Felix w/ Lotringer, Leclaire, Clement at Reid Hall "Le Phallus, la Sainte-Vierge, et les Martiens", 1973; 188784 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Guattari, Felix "Et pourquoi pas une pragmatique generative et transformationnelle?", 1974; 188785 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Guattari, Felix "Pour une [micro]-politque du desir" (Reid Hall lecture), c.1974; 188786 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Guattari, Felix (Textes de colloque), 1980s; 188787 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Guattari, Felix "Le sac de Chez Lancel" (Unpublished), 1980; 188788 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Guattari, Felix "Chaosophy" (1st versions), c.1985; 188789 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Guattari, Felix "Crac en plan pas un pli" (Fiction, orginal typescript), 1986; 188790 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Guattari, Felix (Fictions), 1986; 188791 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Guattari, Felix "Genet Regained", 1986; 188792 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Guattari, Felix and Gilles Deleuze (Interview typescript), undated; 188793 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Guattari, Felix "Pour un regroupement democratique et revolutionnaire" (Unpublished), undated; 188794 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Guyotat, Pierre "Eden, Eden, Eden" (transl. Graham Fox), 1984; 188795 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Hariu, Ichiro "Hyu Shiroo" (w/ transl. by Joseph Love), undated; 188796 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Hass, Amira "Reporting from Ramallah", 2002-3; 188797 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Hass, Amira "Reporting from Ramallah", 2002-3; 188798 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Hell, Richard "The Voidoid" (w/ bio and photo), 1973, 1990s; 188799 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Herbich, Barbara "Affliction, Redemption, and the Written Word in Duras and Antelme", undated; 188843 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Hochschild, Rosemary "Bar Tapes" (Excerpts), 1979; 188844 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Hotswede, Eric (Untitled ms), undated; 188845 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Indiana, Gary (Various mss), c.1980; 188846 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Irigaray, Luce (Book, title unknown), 1999; 188847 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Jackson, Susanne (Various poems), undated; 188848 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Jacoby, Roberto "With the Whole Body", undated; 188849 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Janowitz, Tama "Some Ommited Text for a Semiotic Analysis", undated; 188850 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Jaussely, Jean-Jacques and Madeleine Mitton "Mot a mot", undated; 188851 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Jordan, Ken "Speaking with David Rattray", 1993; 188852 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Joxe, Alain (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), 2000; 188853 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Joxe, Alain "Empire of Chaos", 2001; 188854 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Joxe, Alain and Jaffe (Documents for Joxe's book), undated; 188855 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Joxe, Alain (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated; 188856 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Joxe, Alain "Petites guerres cruelles et paix en panne", undated; 188857 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Kaplan, Alice "Taste Wars: American Professions of French Culture", 1985; 188858 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Katz, Vincent "Pearl" (+ copy of "New York Hello!"), 1992; 188859 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Kaufman, Julie (On "Le degre zero de l'ecriture"), undated; 188860 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Kelley, Mike "Hollywood" and "Baby", undated; 188861 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Kelley, Mike (Various mss), undated; 188862 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Kelsey, John and Jim Fletcher "Special Implants 3-9", undated; 188863 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Kiel, Mark "Barthes/Autumn/Me", undated; 188864 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - King, Kenneth (Various mss), undated; 188865 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Klein, Jason "Chorus for a Psalm", c.1980; 188866 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Kops, Hannah "The Glass Menagerie- A Media Spectacle", undated; 188867 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Krakauer, Daniel "Eight Plays", undated; 188868 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Krakauer, Daniel "The Portable Abyss", undated; 188869 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris and Ann Rower "Sadness at Leaving", 1987; 188870 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris and Ann Rower "Sadness at Leaving", 1988; 188871 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris and Ann Rower "Sadness at Leaving", c.1988; 188872 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris and Ann Rower "Sadness at Leaving" (Film proposal, correspondence), c.1989; 188873 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Fate, The Tribe, & 1000 Modern Coincidences", c.1990; 188874 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick", c.1994; 188875 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick", c.1994; 188876 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick", c.1994; 188877 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick" (Sylvere Lotringer's Dick Journal), c.1994; 188878 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick" (Print-out of original letter exchange between Chris and Sylvere), c.1994; 188879 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick", c.1996; 188880 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick", c.1996; 188881 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia", c.1999; 188882 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia", c.1999; 188883 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia", c.1999; 188884 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Early draft), c.1999; 188885 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Gavin Brice, close to last draft), c.1999; 188886 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Gavin Brice, outtakes), c.1999; 188887 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Letter to Lloyd Phillips, unsent, Mexico), 1999; 188888 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Letters), c.1999; 188889 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Notes, review for Paragon House), c.1999; 188890 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Notes, starvation, biochem, Warren Niodik conversation), c.1999; 188891 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Outtakes), c.1999; 188892 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Paul Thek diaries), c.1999; 188893 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Transcript sans soleil), c.1999; 188894 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Torpor", c.2000; 189005 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris (Willa Cather notes and draft, Horicon Studio), 2002; 189006 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Exterminating Angel", 2007; 189007 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Arnette the Absolute", undated; 189008 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Baby", undated; 189009 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action", undated; 189010 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action", undated; 189011 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action", undated; 189012 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action", undated; 189013 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action", undated; 189014 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action", undated; 189015 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action" (Notes), undated; 189016 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris (Interview), undated; 189017 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Readings from the Diaries of Hugo Ball", undated; 189018 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Singles", undated; 189019 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Terrorists in Love", undated; 189020 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris and Barbara Barg "What Are Women Up To?", undated; 189021 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Kristeva, Julia "The Necessity of Revolt", c.1996; 189022 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Kristeva, Julia "Artaud entre psychose et revolte" (From Artaud conference at MoMA, may be unpublished), undated; 189023 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Lacan, Jacques "The Pure Subject of the Signified" (Original typescript), 1970s; 189024 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Lachman, Ed "Framed" (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated; 189025 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Lazarin, Michael "All Political Economy is Libidinal", undated; 189026 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Lebel, Jean-Jacques "Ginsberg/Flash/Ginsberg" (Edition privee reservee aux amis), 1997; 189027 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Lefebre, Henri "Le possible et l'impossible", undated; 189028 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Levine, Eliba "Trapped", 1976; 189029 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Lindenman, Catherine "Gustave Flaubert: The Origins of Aesthetics" (Table of contents), undated; 189030 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Lindsay, Arto (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated; 189031 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Lisker, Roy "Poli-sexuality and Cosmology", 1979; 189032 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Lofton, Saab (Untitled ms), undated; 189033 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Loselle, Andrea "Cultural Tourism in 20th Century French Literature", 1996; 189034 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Loselle, Andrea "Cultural Tourism in 20th Century French Literature", 1996; 189035 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Ludd, Deran "Sick Burn Cut", 1990; 189036 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Ludd, Deran "Sick Burn Cut", 1991; 189037 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Lyotard, Jean-Francois "Freud According to Cezanne", c.1973; 189038 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - McCormick, Brian "Phantom Quest" and "On Being Grue", 1998; 189063 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - McCormick, Brian "Which-way Data, Mama?", "Malevich" and "Transcendence is Sky", 1998, 1999; 189064 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - McGrath, Patrick "Black Hand of the Raj", undated; 189065 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Mailer, Norman (Interview for High Times), c.1979; 189066 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Menon, Becca "Chronic Solutions", undated; 189067 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Moore, Thurston "How I Became One of the Invisible", 2001; 189068 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Morra, Louis (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated; 189069 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Morris, Rosalind "Interview with Helene Cixous", 1997; 189070 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Mortimer, Alan "Codex 151", 1997; 189071 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Moshenberg, Daniel (Untitled ms), undated; 189072 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Mueller, Cookie (Untitled ms), undated; 189073 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Muller, Heiner "How German Is It?" (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated; 189074 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Muller, Heiner (Interviews), undated; 189075 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Muller, Heiner "Post-Wall Berlin" (Interview), undated; 189076 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Muller, Heiner "The Walls of History" (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated; 189077 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Musil, Robert "The Blackbird" (transl. Peter Wortsman), 1983; 189078 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Myles, Eileen "The Yoga of Anger", 1982; 189079 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Myles, Eileen (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), 1988; 189080 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Myles, Eileen (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), 1988; 189081 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Myles, Eileen (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), 1988; 189082 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Myles, Eileen "The Real Drive", 1988; 189083 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Myles, Eileen "The Real Drive: Poems 1981-1989", c.1989; 189084 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Myles, Eileen "Not Me" (Proofs), 1990; 189085 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Myles, Eileen "Cool for You", undated; 189086 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Myles, Eileen "Cool for You", undated; 189087 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Myles, Eileen "I Am Your President", undated; 189088 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Myles, Eileen "Poems", undated; 189089 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Myles, Eileen "Robin", "Quietude" and "Robert Mapplethorpe Picture", undated; 189090 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Myles, Eileen (Untitled ms), undated; 189091 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Negri, Toni (Interview with Sylvere Lotringer, w/ S.L. annotations and Negri letter), 1986; 189092 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Negri, Toni (Interview with Sylvere Lotringer, w/ letter from Gilles Labelle), c.1987; 189093 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Negri, Toni (Interview with Sylvere Lotringer, cassette transcription), c.1987; 189094 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Negri, Toni (Interview with Sylvere Lotringer, cassette #1), c.1987; 189095 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Negri, Toni "Theses", 1989; 189096 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Negri, Toni "Postmoderno", c.1990; 189097 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Negri, Toni (Transcript of interview/trial), undated; 189098 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Overlie, Mary (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated; 189099 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Pell, Derek "Assassination Rhapsody", undated; 189100 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Peoples, David and Janet "Twelve Monkeys", 1994; 189101 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Perez, Rolando Jr. "On An(archy) and Schizoanalysis", 1986; 189102 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Perez, Rolando Jr. "Love and Hatred of French Theory in Capitalist America", c.2001; 189103 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Perrin, Veronique "Les bizarreries de la pudeur", undated; 189104 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Perry, John "Psychosis & Visionary States", 1976; 189105 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Phillips, Cynthia "Thesis on Koons", c.1996; 189106 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Pickering, Shawn "Poems", undated; 189107 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Poe, Amos (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated; 189108 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Preston, John "A Story Dedicated to Jason", undated; 189109 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Preston, John "Stop Over in Boston", "Weekend in NYC", "Mineshaft" and "Tenth Welt", undated; 189110 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Rainer, Yvonne "Journeys from Berlin/1971" (w/ S.L. notes), 1980; 189111 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Rammellzee "Ionic Treatise on Gothic Futurism", 1979; 189112 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Raskin, Jimmy "The Prologue", undated; 189113 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Rattray, David "In Nomine", c.1991; 189114 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Rattray, David "Artaud's Cane", 1992; 189115 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Rattray, David "How I Became One of the Invisible", c.1992; 189116 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Rattray, David "How I Became One of the Invisible", c.1992; 189117 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Rattray, David "How I Became One of the Invisible" (Proofs), 1992; 189118 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Rattray, David "The Angel" (w/ copy of interview by Ken Jordan), undated; 189119 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Rattray, David "La mort difficile- Translator's Introduction", undated; 189120 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Rattray, David "Sounds of the River Naranjana", undated; 189121 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Ray, Susan "The Adventures of Binnie the Kid", undated; 189122 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Reich, Steve (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated; 189123 (Box 28, Folder 25)